ANDREW MARCUS

123 Your Street Philadelphia, PA 12345 andrewrnarcus@ex.ample.com (123) 456-7890

A Construction Manager with six years of experience specializing in civil engineering, construction management, project leadership, and building codes, A proven track record of managing residential construction projects. A strong history of identifying strategies to execute projects ahead of schedule and under budget.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT (BSCMJ

Temple University, Philadelphia, PA September 2011 - May 2015

KEY SKILLS

- Residential Construction
- Home Renovation
- Client Relations
- · Inventory Management
- OSH A Safety

CERTIFICATIONS

 Certified Construction Manager (CCM), Awarded 2017

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CONSTRUCTION MANAGER
South Philly Construction Partners,
Philadelphia, PA
April 2017 - Present

- Oversee the construction of a 4K sq. Ft. custom home, gather project requirements, manage a \$1.5M budget, and ensure alignment with client specifications
- Manage a \$300K project for new home renovations, establish project scope, conduct strategic planning, and deliver project \$50K under budget
- Lead teams of 10-15 subcontractors throughout the project lifecycle, assign project responsibilities, and provide support to ensure quality deliverables

ASSISTANT CONSTRUCTION MANAGER Hamilton Construction Co., Philadelphia, PA

May 2015 - April 2017

- Provided support to the construction manager for the execution of construction projects for residential homes valued at \$200K-\$500K
- Evaluated project blueprints, attended meetings with clients prior to construction to mitigate risks and resolve issues, and provided recommendations to enhance design
- Coordinated daily logistics and interfaced with external contractors throughout construction to identify solutions to roadblocks and improve project timelines